BGM
I was thinking of doing a world theme.
I'm thinking of changing the country for each member.
I'm planning to change the country for each member.
First of all, I'm going to choose Denmark.
Denmark
Like this.
You've done a makeover in both countries, right?
Yes, I am.
That's weird.
It must be hard.
As for Chloe's costume style, I think it's fine.
Yes, please.
It's cute.
It's adorable.
Amazing.
That's great.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's horrible.
Chloe's been hit right here.
He's standing right here.
Or a goat.
It's not a sheep?
It's not a sheep.
Not a sheep?
Not a sheep.
Not a sheep?Even a sheep?
Which would you prefer, sheep or goat?
Sheep?
A duck.
You want to take it?
Yes, please.
Oh, my God!
A babysitter!
Folk.
Like the Hausdembos, right?
Yeah, like a Haus den Bosch or something like that.
Maybe I'll get a headdress like that.
I'd like to do something like that.
Something like that.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It looks so real right now.
Can I take a picture with this too?
It's so cute.
I think it's the one we didn't have before.
What?
I don't know what to do.
Yes, on the hair.
I think it's better if it's in the back so I can see your face.
Okay, cut.
I think that's good.
One more thing.
About this much, right?
About this much?
I don't know.
You don't know?
If I put it in, it might get really big.
Laughs.
LOL!
Well, that's great.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
Since it will start here
And your own image.
I'm looking forward to it.
I didn't know what everyone else was thinking
I didn't know what everyone was thinking.
I didn't know what everyone was thinking, so when I opened the dressing room
It was so interesting.
I didn't care who won.
I'd like to win, too.
I'd love to win, but I'd also like to see what goes on inside a stranger's head in a fight.
I'd like to see that.
Donut was sleeping backstage.
LOL.
I want to get the word out.
It's a franchise tour.
It's not just a fan club tour.
I want it to be more than just a fan club tour.
I want it to be something like
I want to create a buzz
I want to get the word out
Natalie News or something.
I want to be on Yahoo News.
I want to be Yahoo News.
My home is in
Denmark.
Scandinavian.
It's like
It's like something out of Helmer's Mail.
Woman pouring milk
this
is
a lifetime
after a lifetime after a lifetime.
I got to order this one last time.
I feel like I've made it.
The outfit looks like this.
The other day at the fitting.
And the apron that wasn't there
It's all done and here it is.
On the top.
It's so cute, isn't it?
The shoes are
They look great.
Loafers?
And the socks.
Look at the
Spice
And the outfit.
Costume too
Spice
Costumes
We'd like to match each member's image with the costumes that match their feeling and not ethnic ones.
I think they will be absolutely cute.
Well, the setlist will be a late show, for example, and Yakudo will be the same.
Yakudo, See All Climb, Hedic, Laila, and so on.
We'll also include songs inspired by strange countries, like Sea All Crime, Hedic, Laila, etc.
But that's not enough songs.
I'd like to divide it into unit songs, Konzabets, and Paradise.
I hope we can perform them separately.
We would like to show that there are many different worlds and that Young Parade has many different things to offer.
Please vote for us!